pornz.tv 2007-12-29

# Private Policy

**Effective Date: May 1, 2007**

THIS PRIVACY AND INFORMATION SECURITY POLICY COVERS PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION ("PII" OR "INFORMATION") COLLECTED BY ENOM, INC. (“ENOM”) RELATING TO A USER OF: (A) THIS PERSONAL WEBSITE (THIS “SITE”); AND (B) THE WEBSITE LOCATED AT HTTP://WWW.CHANNELME.TV (THE “SERVICES INTERFACE”). ENOM, WHICH OPERATES THE SERVICES INTERFACE, IS THE PRIMARY REGISTRAR, WEB HOST, AND PROVIDER OF CERTAIN VALUE-ADDED SERVICES TO THE OWNER AND OPERATOR OF THIS SITE (THE “SITE OPERATOR”). ENOM DOES NOT OWN OR OPERATE THIS SITE. 

THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT GOVERN THE WAY THE SITE OPERATOR COLLECTS, USE, OR DISCLOSES INFORMATION ABOUT YOU OBTAINED IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THIS SITE. THE SITE OPERATOR’S COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF THE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU OBTAINED IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THIS SITE IS GOVERNED BY THE SITE OPERATOR’S OWN PRIVACY POLICIES AND PROCEDURES. IF THE SITE OPERATOR HAS NOT POSTED A PRIVACY POLICY ON THIS SITE, THE SITE OWNER IS UNRESTRICTED IN ITS ABILITY TO COLLECT, ACCESS, PRESERVE, AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION. YOU MAY DIRECT YOUR INQUIRIES TO THE SITE OPERATOR THROUGH THIS [LINK](). 

**Who We Are. We are eNom, Inc** ( **"eNom," "we," "us,"** or **"our"** ). The Site provides individuals with the opportunity to create personal profiles, to post content and to share their ideas with others. In the context of pursuing that business, as further described below, we collect various information, including PII, from and about the individuals who either contribute Content to or visit the Site. 

**How does this Policy relate to my use of the Site?** This Policy is part of and incorporated into the Terms of Use for the Site, the contract between you and the Site Operator that governs the Site. That means provisions of those terms impact this Policy, so if you have not read the  Terms of Use, read them now by clicking on the link. 

**BY PROVIDING PII OR OTHER INFORMATION TO US OR BY USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY AND THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED HEREIN** and the Terms of Use. 

## eNom Reserves the Right to Share Information with Third Parties.

We reserve the right to share Information with third parties. You should carefully review this Policy and determine if you are comfortable with the kinds of information we collect. If you do not want us to collect information about you, do not provide us information or use the Site or Services Interface. 

In general, we use PII to verify, evaluate, process, respond to, communicate about, investigate and enforce our rights and Content You may submit. We tend to use non-PII for purposes such as measuring the number of visitors to sections of the Site and Services Interface, making the Site and Services Interface more useful to visitors, and optimizing the relevancy of Content, services, and advertisements delivered to our users. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site and the Services Interface, track user's movement, and gather Internet traffic and usage data and demographic information. 

We do share Information with third parties. Some of the ways we disclose Information are described below. 

  * **Advertisers:** We will share profile, Internet traffic and usage data, and profile and demographic information with advertisers and advertising consultants.
  * **Service Third Parties:** We contract with affiliated and non-affiliated third parties to provide specific services to Us or to You on our behalf. Examples include providing marketing assistance, providing customer services, sending postal mail and email to you, removing repetitive information from customer lists, and analyzing data. These persons have access to personal information needed to perform their functions.
  * **Business Transfer:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets, or engage in transfers in acquisitions, mergers, restructuring, insolvency proceedings, changes of control or operations or the like. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets, and Your Information may be subject to such a transfer. In the event of a transfer of data in connection with a business transfer, your data will continue to be subject to this privacy policy or one no less protective of your rights than this one. 
  * **Affiliates.** We may share customer information with our current affiliates or those entities who later become our affiliates. An affiliate is a person or entity who we control, who controls us, or who is under common control with us.
  * **Compliance:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law, to respond to legal process; to make disclosures under programs intended to prevent potential crimes or investigate persons; enforce or apply agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of eNom, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

We reserve the right to do the above and the following worldwide: use, access (or bar access to), process, disclose, display, share, transfer, store, sell, retain, commingle, investigate, verify, prove and otherwise deal with, voluntarily or as required by law, (collectively "Disclose") all PII, non-PII and other information. We may Disclose the foregoing internally or to third parties or through any databases for any purpose or, in our discretion, to help prevent or address perceived harm, damage or loss to us or others. 

The above descriptions are not a list of all possible Disclosures we may make. This Policy is intended to aid your understanding of our general practices. 

## What Personal Information About Me Does eNom Gather?

  * **Information You Give Us:**

We collect any information you enter on the Site or the Services Interface, during the registration process of creating a personal profile, or give us in any other way (such as through an email or letter). We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, providing our services, our business operations, the maintenance of your Account and communicating with you, all as described in greater detail below. 

The information that we collect varies, but our registration forms generally require that you provide us with your user name, birthday and e-mail address, and that you create and provide us with a password. We may also request certain other information, such as your actual first and last name, gender and postal or zip code. 

Some of the information that we collect is provided by you when you set up an account. Under the Terms of Use, You must set up an account ("Account") by completing the registration process required by the Site. You agree to provide accurate and complete information during the registration process. You also agree that You will maintain and update such information to ensure its accuracy and completeness at all times. 

You agree not to provide PII or confidential or sensitive information unless: (1) you have obtained any required permission to do so under applicable law and, (2) for PII relating to someone other than You, You have informed the person whose data will be included that their PII will be subject to this Policy and You have obtained their consent to this Policy. You must do this even if an inability to obtain permission means that You cannot submit Content or other information. By providing information to us, you represent and warrant that you have made all required disclosures and obtained all required permissions. 

  * **Automatic Information:**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us, the Services Interface, or the Site. For example, like many Internet companies, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the Site or the Services Interface. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. We use persistent, identifying cookies to remember your information and to link your activities to You. 

Our cookies collect at least the following: 

    * the domain name and host from which you access the Internet and the Internet address of the site from which you direct-linked to ours;
    * the date and time you access the Site or the Services Interface and pages you visit;
    * your computer’s IP address and information about its operating system, platform and the Web browser type and version you use; and
    * information to combat fraud or misuse.

While you can take steps to warn of, block or disable cookies, if you do, the Site and Services Interface won’t function and/or appear as we have designed it. Nonetheless, if you want to take these steps, you can do so by following the instructions associated with your particular browser. 

In our e-mails to you, we use "pixel tags" to determine if your email software or service can display html-formatted e-mail (this helps us optimize the size of our e-mail messages and conserve bandwidth). Some of the businesses that place advertisements and other content on the Site or Services Interface may use cookies on our site. If you click on an advertisement, for example, a cookie might be placed on your computer. However, we have no access to or control over these companies, their privacy policies or their cookies, and their practice and policies may change from time to time so you should read their privacy policies and decide whether they are acceptable to You. 

_We generally will retain_ information for as long as required, allowed or we believe it useful, but do not undertake retention obligations. We may dispose of information in our discretion without notice, subject to applicable law. You must keep your own, separate records. 

## How Secure Is Information About Me?

  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer or other internet access device. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. Your e-mails to us are not necessarily secure against interception so do not include sensitive information in them - we generally will not ask for passwords or the like in an email and you should assume that if you get such a request, it might be fraudulent.
  * You agree not to enter information on the Site or the Services Interface if You (or anyone else whose information you enter) desire a higher level of security than we describe above or if You have not obtained any appropriate consents.

**WE DO NOT GUARANTEE SECURITY.** Neither people nor security systems are foolproof, including encryption systems, and people can commit intentional crimes, make mistakes or fail to follow policies **YOU ASSUME THE RISK OF ANY INADEQUACY OR FAILURE OF SECURITY AND AGREE TO DO WHAT YOU REASONABLY CAN TO PROMOTE SECURITY.** If applicable law imposes any non-disclaimable duty (if any), you agree that the standard used to measure our compliance with that duty will be one of intentional misconduct.

## CHOICE

If you are not comfortable with this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use, or the Disclosures we may make, please do not provide us with PII or other information or Content or otherwise use the Site or the Services Interface. 

## Links

The Site and the Services Interface contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave the Site or the Services Interface and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that may collect their personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Site and the Services Interface.

## ACCESS

Information relating to our programs is not necessarily maintained in a retrievable form. However, you may make changes, corrections or updates to some PII provided through this Site which we use for communications with you, by contacting [ support@channelme.tv](mailto:support@channelme.tv). We may keep a record of all information that is changed (including deletions) and Disclose it for any lawful purpose. We may determine what may be changed (e.g., if we are required to keep track of certain kinds of transactions, you may not change relevant information).

## Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

  * If you choose to visit the Services Interface or the Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and the Terms of Use for the Site, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of Washington. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check this Site and the Services Interface frequently to see recent changes. **Your Consent to Email Notice:** We generally do not send "commercial e-mails" (e.g., e-mails whose primary purpose is to advertise a product or service); if we do, we will provide any "opt-out" choice required by the federal CAN-SPAM Act. We reserve the right to communicate with you about any subject matter of the Terms or any other subject matter not prohibited by law.
  * If we are required to disclose or provide notice of invasion of certain security systems, we will do so when required by sending notice to any email address provided to us by you at the time that you registered. If applicable state law does not permit the giving of notice by email, we will provide notice by other lawful means.
  * **Identity Theft.** If You believe that You are a victim of identity theft entitled by law to request information from us, write us at Our Legal Notice Address (see the "Legal Notices" section of the Terms or the next section of this Privacy Policy) and we will let you know what additional information you must provide to us. **After we have received that information, we will supply without charge the information legally required to be disclosed that we then have, subject to applicable law and reserving all of our rights and defenses.**

## CONTACT INFORMATION AND INFORMATION ABOUT ENFORCEMENT OF OUR POLICY:

**Contacting Us & Our Address for Legal Notices; Notices to You.** For customer service matters, you may email us at [support@channelme.tv](mailto:support@channelme.tv). To send us a legal notice, mail it by certified mail (return receipt requested) or via recognized overnight carrier to eNom Legal Department, 15801 NE 24th St. Bellevue, WA 98008 (our " **Address for Legal Notices** "). When we need to contact you, including when we give a legal notice, you agree that we may do so to a postal or email address that we have on file for you and/or may post notice on the Services Interface. It is important for you to update your address information periodically. 

This Policy is part of the Site Terms. If there is an inconsistency between the Terms and this Policy, the latest version of this Policy controls. If you think we have failed to comply with this Policy, you may contact us at Our Address for Legal Notices. 

eNom is a registered trademark of eNom, Inc. in the United States and/or other countries.
